<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Gablestone Quest</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_toolbar">Toolbar</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tabbed">TabbedActivity</string>
    <string name="intro_title">Gablestones Quest in Amsterdam</string>
    <string name="about_gable_stones">Explore Amsterdam and discover unique details of the city\'s rich history. Historic houses and mansions were often decorated with gable stones: carved and painted stone tablets fixed on the facade. They gave information about the owner or the business, sometimes straightforward, sometimes through subtle hints or even riddles. Before street names and house numbers were established the location of a house was referred by the gable stone.</string>
    <string name="topic_tour">Quest: Find the rabbits</string>
    <string name="explanation">Start the quest and search for the specific gable stones. Your missions consists of 10 clues, locate the gable stones and/or other parts of a house as described in the clues. Complete all items, discover hidden gems while emerging in the history of Amsterdam. Explore Amsterdam in an unique and memorable way.</string>
    <string name="intro_instruction1"> - Start your quest: the clues will lead you to the gable stones </string>
    <string name="intro_instruction2"> - Locate the gable stones in Map</string>
    <string name="intro_instruction3"> - Solve the clues</string>
    <string name="intro_enjoy">Explore and Enjoy!</string>
    <!--    Permissions    -->
    <string name="permission_rationale_location">Access to the location service is required to demonstrate the "Show me my current location on the map" feature, which shows your current location on the map.</string>
    <string name="location_permission_denied">This app requires location permission to enable the "Show me my current location on the map" functionality. Please try again and grant access to use the location.\nIf the permission has been permanently denied, it can be enabled from the System Settings &gt; Apps &gt; \'Google Maps API Demos\'.</string>
    <string name="permission_required_toast">Location permission is required to show your location on the map.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_clue_detail_activiy">Clues Details</string>

    <!--Gable Stones-->
    <string name="street_address_1">Anjelierstraat 40</string>
    <string name="street_address_2">Westermarkt 1</string>
    <string name="street_address_3">Damrak 15</string>
    <string name="gablestone_1">Reading Chicken</string>
    <string name="gablestone_2">Weather Chicken</string>
    <string name="gablestone_3">Golden Egg</string>

    <!--Headers of fragments and activities-->
    <string name="stone_detail">Clue Detail</string>



</resources>
